Guide to the Nasher Museum of Art records, 1947-2018, bulk 1990s-2018 UA.07.10.0002
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Accession UA2020.0014
  - 4 minutes 33 seconds: Composer John Cage's work for the piano dedicated to Irwin Kremen, April 12, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Collectors Conversation: E. Blake Byrne with Kim Rorschach, April 14, 2007 (Box 14)
  - The Art of Sampling: Ninth Wonder, Marc Anthony Neal, Kawachi Clemmons, April 17, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Lecture: On the Making of the Re'eh Series and Its Iconography, April 29, 2007 (Box 14)
  - El Greco Lecture, May 5, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Rick Powell, May 22, 2007 (Box 14)
  - "The State of Things" WUNC-FM, June 4, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Curators Panel: Kim Rorschach, Trevor Schoonmaker, Anee Schroder, Andy Rothschild, New at the Nasher, July 18, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Opening Event: States of Mind: Dan and Lia Perjovschi, August 29, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Perspectives on Romanian Culture: Then and Now, August 30, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Jennifer Neils Lecture, September 11, 2007 (Box 14)
  - David Harrington Lecture, September 13, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Barbara and Andrew Rothschild Lecture: Kehinde Wiley, September 15, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Lecture: Faith Wilding: Cyberfeminism, Bioart, and Feminist Art, September 20, 2007 (Box 14)
  - JB Duke Founders Society Dinner: "Reflecting on the Arts: A Tribute to Ray Nasher", September 28, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Triangle Gallery, October 10, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Lecture: Robin D.G. Kelley: A Following Monk Festival Event, October 26, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Talk and Booksigning: Alex Harris, November 16, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Christopher Cozier, January 23, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Panel Discussion: Kara Walker, January 17, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Tarheel Traveler at the Nasher Museum WRAL-TV, February 7, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Barkley L. Hendricks: Birth of the Cool Opening and DJ Party, February 7, 2008 (Box 14)
  - "Hip-Hop Sampling Soul: Questlove & 9th Wonder", February 20, 2008 (Box 14)
  - FESTAC 77 to Venice 07: Contemporary Art, Africa, and the Global Exhibit, March 1, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Contemporary Art Lecture, March 26, 2008 (Box 14)
  - El Greco Lecture, August 28, 2008 (Box 14)
  - El Greco to Velazquez, September 16, 2008; 2 items (Box 14)
    CD and DVD
  - El Greco: "The Historical and Religious Context in 17th Century Spain", September 28, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Barkley L. Hendricks Lecture, October 16, 2008 (Box 14)
  - Barkley Hendricks Experience, April 26, 2001 (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 2006; 4 items (Box 14)
  - Roconey Labor, January 29, 2007 (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 2008; 7 items (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 2009; 16 items (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 2010; 11 items (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 2011; 3 items (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 2012; 5 items (Box 14)
  - Nasher Lectures, 12 items (Box 14)
  - Sarah in Boston, 3 items (Box 14)
  - Assorted Lectures and Events, 13 items (Box 14)
  - Kimerly Rorschach UNC-TV, October 28, 2005; 2 items (Box 15)
    VHS, copies
  - Nasher Slide Show of Rafael Vinoly's Architectural Process, 2005 (Box 15)
  - Interview with Kimerly Rorschach with "North Carolina Now", August 16, 2005; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Local News Broadcasts of Grand Opening, September 28, 2005; October 2, 2005; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Eve Sussman and the Rufus Corporation: The Rape of the Sabine Women Trailer, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Grant Hill Profile on CBS Sunday Morning, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Inside Basketball with Coach K Grant Hill Art Collection Feature, March 2006 (Box 15)
  - Collector's Conversation: Grant Hill Lecture featuring Calvin Hill and Coach K, March 7, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Grant Hill: Donation to Nasher Museum, March 7, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Cold Pizza: Grant Hill Art Collection Interview with Chris Broussard, March 21, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Keeping Up with the Joneses: Short Profile of Nasher, Nasher Café, and Hill Collection, April 22, 2006 (Box 15)
  - "The State of Things" Eve Sussman, September 7, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Barbara and Andrew Rothschild Lecture: Eve Sussman and the Rufus Corporation, September 7, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Georges Rousse Lecture: Durham Community Project, September 13, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Collector's Conversation: Jason Rubell with Kimerly Rorschach, September 14, 2006; 2 items (Box 15)
  - Friends Lecture Series: Kim Rorschach on Contemporary Art, September 21, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Nasher One Year Anniversary, October 5, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Curator's Conversation: Between Past and Future Exhibition Curators Wu Hung and Christopher Phillips, October 25, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Artist Panel Discussion: Between Past and Future, October 25, 2006 (Box 15)
  - "Modern Art from China", October 26, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Artist Lecture: Jaume Plensa, October 29, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Artist Lecture: Petah Coyne, November 2, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Friends Lecture Series: Trevor Schoonmaker "Approaching Contemporary Art", November 9, 2006 (Box 15)
  - SMART START, November 18, 2006 (Box 15)
  - Annual Semans Lecture: Thomas Krens, February 21, 2007 (Box 15)
  - The State of Things WUNC-FM, March 29, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Lecture: John Seely Brown (HASTAC), April 19, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Lecture: Maurice Benayoun "Digital Wanderings: From Immersion to Critical Fusion", September 12, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Barkely Hendricks Lecture, October 15, 2007 (Box 15)
  - Young Friends: Gallery Tour: Making of El Greco to Velazquez, March 18, 2008 (Box 15)
  - Nasher Opening and Construction, 2005-2006; 22 items (Box 16)
    CD
  - Assorted Images and Events, 2005; 5 items (Box 16)
  - Assorted Images and Events, 2006; 17 items (Box 16)
  - Assorted Images and Events, 2007-2008; 17 items (Box 16)
  - Assorted Images and Events, 2008; 23 items (Box 16)
  - Sacred Beauty Illuminated Manuscripts Photos, 2010 (Box 16)
  - Duke Police, 2 items (Box 16)
  - Interviews, 2013-2015; 12 items (Box 16)
  - Color Correction, 5 items (Box 16)
  - Documentaries, 15 items (Box 16)
  - Permanent Collection, 6 items (Box 16)
  - Collecting Matisse and Modern Masters, 21 items (Box 16)
  - Miscellaneous, 27 items (Box 16)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 17)
  - Sabine Women Clippings (Box 17)
  - Between Past and Future: New Photography & Video from China Clippings (Box 17)
  - Mexico City Clippings (Box 17)
  - William Cordova Clippings (Box 17)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 17)
  - Bloomsbury Clippings (Box 17)
  - Untitled Folder (Box 17)
  - Perjovschi Clippings (Box 17)
  - Bearden Clippings (Box 17)
  - Grant Hill Clippings (Box 17)
  - Rubell Family Collection Clippings (Box 17)
  - George Rousse Clippings (Box 17)
  - Kremen Clippings (Box 17)
  - Miscellaneous (Box 17)
  - Kimerly Rorschach UNC-TV, October 28, 2005 (Box 17)
  - Mini-Disc CDs: Exhibitions (Box 17)
  - Loose Oversize Clippings (Box 17)
  - Assorted Print Collatoral (Box 18)